czechcash.com 2017-11-13

# CzechCASH

CZECHCASH affiliate program gives you an unbeatable opportunity to earn 50% commission from each visitor and all of its downloading for all the time. A payment of commission is done every 14 days. There is an option to pay by checks or transfer to an account. Don't waste time and sign up now!

## 

  * 40+ original, exclusive sites
  * Beautiful czech amateurs
  * High-converting sites to promote
  * Payouts by wire and Paypal
  * Cutting-edge promo tools
  * Great support

##  PRIVACY POLICY 

Your privacy is of utmost importance to us. This Privacy Policy (the "Policy") applies to the NETLOOK s.r.o. (the "Company") family of websites (the "Sites"). These include CZECHAV.COM, CZECHAMATEURS.COM, CZECHCASTING.COM, CZECHFIRSTVIDEO.COM, CZECHGANGBANG.COM, CZECHLESBIANS.COM, CZECHMEGASWINGERS.COM, CZECHPARTIES.COM, CZECHSTREETS.COM, CZECHGAV.COM, CZECHGAYCASTING.COM, CZECHCASH.COM CZECHTOILETS.COM, CZECHHOMEORGY.COM and all other sites at which this Policy appears and which are owned/controlled by the Company. As noted below, please be aware that we may change our Privacy Policy in the future and it is your obligation to review this Privacy Policy from time to time and the effective date listed with it. 

**THIS IS AN ADULTS ONLY SERVICE.** We will suspend or terminate any accounts which we believe are being used by anyone under the age of eighteen (18) years old or the age of majority in the jurisdiction in which you view the Sites; additionally, we reserve the right to report such person to the proper authorities along with all information provided to us by or with respect to such person. 

**Disclosures Made as Necessitated by Law or Safety**  
Your name, physical address, phone number and password are considered confidential. However, all information you provide to us may be shared with other third parties as necessary to comply with applicable law, to cooperate with law enforcement and the court system. 

**The Specific Information We Will Need**  
During sign up we require that you provide us with certain information which may include Account Data (i.e., your name, physical address, e-mail address, phone number, username, and password), Financial Data (i.e., credit card/billing information) along with specified Demographic Information. Demographic Information may include IP address(es), referring website information, Internet browser used, zip code and/or other data regarding search history, browsing history, registration and user history. 

**How is this Information Used?**   
Financial Data will only be shared with third party processors as necessary to initiate and complete any orders placed by your account.   
We may use cookies and Demographic Information to better your experience on the Sites by allowing us to tailor your experience on the Sites according to your preferences and what we think may appeal to you based on such Demographic Information. Aggregate, non-individual membership Demographic Information may be shared with third parties with whom we have a direct or indirect relationship who may offer products or services we believe you may be interested in. We may also share the aggregate Demographic Information with third parties for the purposes of analyzing usage data, maintaining servers and other purposes relating to maintaining and improving our service and the Sites. 

**You Are Responsible For Information You Provide to Third Parties**   
We process credit card transactions via industry standard encryption through third party processors, who only use your information for that purpose. Financial Data is considered private information and will not be shared by us with third parties except with your authorization and as necessary to carry out orders placed by you with the understanding by you that such transaction(s) may be subject to the rules and policies of such third party. Financial or other Data provided by you to any companies or websites advertising on the Sites or in response to e-mails sent to you by the Sites are not governed by this Privacy Policy. Any information provided by you to a third party, and any transaction with such a third party, is subject to that third party`s terms and conditions and privacy policy. 

**E-mails From Us and use of Your E-mail Address**  
Your e-mail address will be used by us to contact you when we have special offers or other information to provide you. Such information may include, without limitation, new services offered by us, information relating to your account and other information related to your subscription to the Sites. We may send you e-mails prior to and after you have terminated your membership to our service until such time as you advise us, in accordance with the procedures explained below, that you no longer wish to receive e-mail from us. If you no longer wish to receive e-mails from us please unsubscribe from from our mailing list by sending us an e-mail to info@czechav.com. We and our advertising partners fully comply with the federal CAN-SPAM Act and as such all e-mails from us and our advertising partners will always, among other required disclosures, have a place for you to opt out of receipt of further e-mail correspondence. Please note we will never send you an e-mail directly or through our marketing partners without your consent. Please immediately report any e-mails you may receive, without your prior authorization, that purport to promote the Sites. 

**Advertisements**  
We utilize the services of outside advertising agencies to advertise our services and goods and/or services offered by third parties. Either we or our advertising agencies may use cookies and/or action tags to measure advertising effectiveness on an anonymous basis. Some e-mails from us may contain advertisements from companies unrelated to the Sites. Should you elect to visit any such advertiser’s website, we cannot, and do not, make any representations about applicable terms and conditions or privacy policies for such advertisers’ websites. If you choose to make any purchases on such sites or accept any offers from such companies, we may provide your information, including Financial Data, to the advertiser as necessary to your request. Finally, we cannot, and do not, make any representations about the privacy policies or terms and conditions of advertisements appearing anywhere on our service, whether through our website or e-mails, this is regardless of whether or not there may be any mentions of or references to any or all of the Sites on such advertisers’ website(s). 

**Changes to the Privacy Policy**  
We may change this privacy policy at any time. You agree that we are under no duty to send you notice of such changes. Instead it is your responsibility to check this Privacy Policy from time to time. No change in the privacy policy will be effective until thirty (30) days after it is posted, unless the privacy policy has clear language indicating otherwise. 

**Changes in the Ownership of the Sites**   
The Sites are a growing online service. As such, we may have the occasion to buy or sell assets, including but not limited to merger, dissolution, and transfer of ownership. Depending upon the nature of the transaction, we may share any and all data provided by you to us (including Financial Data and Account Information) with third parties, as necessary to initiate, investigate or complete any such transaction(s). 

In Prague, 01.07.2012

* * *
